https://www.lovedignity.com/privacy-policy/

HomeDatingDating TipsRomantic Date IdeasRelationshipBreakups & RebuildingRelationship ProblemsTips & AdviceLoveLove LettersLove QuotesLove SongsMarriageRing Buying TipsWedding PlaningMarriage ProposalMarriage ProblemsGet Your Ex BackGet Your Boyfriend BackGet Your Girlfriend BackTips & Advice For BothReviewsDating SitesDating GuidesEx Back GuidesRelationship GuidesSexualityMoreSexPsychologyHave a Break!Gift IdeasHomeHomepage»Privacy PolicyLove Dignity Inc. (“Love Dignity“) operates Lovedignity.com and may operate other websites. It is Love Dignity’s policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our websites.Website VisitorsLike most website operators, Love Dignity collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. Love Dignity’s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how Love Dignity’s visitors use its website. From time to time, Love Dignity may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.Love Dignity also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses for logged in users and for users leaving comments on LoveDignity.com blogs/sites. Love Dignity only discloses logged in user and commenter IP addresses under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information as described below, except that commenter IP addresses and email addresses are visible and disclosed to the administrators of the blog/site where the comment was left.Gathering of Personally-Identifying InformationCertain visitors to Love Dignity’s websites choose to interact with Love Dignity in ways that require Love Dignity to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that Love Dignity gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who sign up at LoveDignity.com to provide a username and email address. Those who engage in transactions with Love Dignity are asked to provide additional information, including as necessary the personal and financial information required to process those transactions. In each case, Love Dignity collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor’s interaction with Love Dignity. Love Dignity does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.Aggregated StatisticsLove Dignity may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its websites. Love Dignity may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, Love Dignity does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below.Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying InformationLove Dignity discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on Love Dignity’s behalf or to provide services available at Love Dignity’s websites, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using Love Dignity’s websites, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. Love Dignity will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, Love Dignity discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only in response to a subpoena, court order or other governmental request, or when Love Dignity believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of Love Dignity, third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered user of an Love Dignity website and have supplied your email address, Love Dignity may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what’s going on with Love Dignity and our products. If you send us a request (for example via email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. Love Dignity takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.CookiesA cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. Love Dignity uses cookies to help Love Dignity identify and track visitors, their usage of Love Dignity website, and their website access preferences. Love Dignity visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using Love Dignity’s websites, with the drawback that certain features of Love Dignity’s websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.Business TransfersIf Love Dignity, or substantially all of its assets, were acquired, or in the unlikely event that Love Dignity goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of Love Dignity may continue to use your personal information as set forth in this policy.AdsAds appearing on any of our websites may be delivered to users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by Love Dignity and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.Privacy Policy ChangesAlthough most changes are likely to be minor, Love Dignity may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in Love Dignity’s sole discretion. Love Dignity encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. If you have a Lovedignity.com account, you might also receive an alert informing you of these changes. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.Leave a Reply Cancel replyYour email address will not be published. Required fields are marked *CommentName * Email * Website
Recent Posts
What Is a Simp? Gen Z & TikTok Slang Explained December 10, 2020
7 Romantic Travel Destinations for Couples December 6, 2020
5 Red Flags Indicating That You’re in the Wrong Relationship December 6, 2020
Old Fashioned Romantic Gestures to Woo the Modern Woman November 28, 2020
Being Prudent – 5 Things to Check Before Getting Married November 28, 2020
Recent Reviews
1 Sex Messenger Review – #1 Adult Dating Community in Your Area! July 7, 2020 8.8
2 The Hard Wood Tonic System Review May 25, 2020 9.0
3 Micheal Fiore’s Make Him Worship You Review March 24, 2020 8.5
4 E.D. Elixir Review – An Effective Erectile Dysfunction Treatment? October 6, 2019 8.5
5 ManPlus – #1 RATED Male Enhancement Pills Review September 17, 2019 8.8
